Tufts Weekly UP056
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 February 10; UP056.001.049.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 February 17; UP056.001.049.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 February 24; UP056.001.049.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 49)
    John Ahern. Appointed Sports Publicity Director. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 March 02; UP056.001.049.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 March 09; UP056.001.049.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 March 16; UP056.001.049.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 March 23; UP056.001.049.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 March 30; UP056.001.049.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 April 13; UP056.001.049.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 April 18; UP056.001.049.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 April 21; UP056.001.049.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 April 25; UP056.001.049.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 April 28; UP056.001.049.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 May 02; UP056.001.049.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 May 05; UP056.001.049.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 May 09; UP056.001.049.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
    [Administration] Committee on Academic Standing establishes probation criteria. p. 5. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 May 12; UP056.001.049.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
    [Alpha Sigma Phi] Administration objects to house painted black {includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 May 16; UP056.001.049.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 May 19; UP056.001.049.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 September 14; UP056.001.050.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 September 21; UP056.001.050.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 September 28; UP056.001.050.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of; [Alpha Xi Delta] Jackson sorority withdrew from national group because of discriminatory policies, to continue locally
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 October 05; UP056.001.050.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 October 11; UP056.001.050.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 October 19; UP056.001.050.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 October 26; UP056.001.050.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [The Aesthetes] Organized October 16, 1956, p. 8.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 November 02; UP056.001.050.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Academic Honors; p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 November 09; UP056.001.050.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 November 17; UP056.001.050.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 November 30; UP056.001.050.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 December 07; UP056.001.050.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [Administration] (Buckley, James) Traffic Commission analyzes traffic problems; plans campus safety drive. p. 5.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1956 December 14; UP056.001.050.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [Administration] (Buckley, James) Traffic Commission analyzes traffic problems; plans campus safety drive. (photos) p. 1. [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly ALpha Xi Delta). Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 January 11; UP056.001.050.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 February 08; UP056.001.050.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 February 15; UP056.001.050.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [alumni association] Martin L. Albert, Secretary Nickless tells what Tufts does to hold interest in the college
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 February 21; UP056.001.050.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 March 01; UP056.001.050.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 March 08; UP056.001.050.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 March 15; UP056.001.050.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 March 22; UP056.001.050.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Alpha Kappa Delta; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 April 01; UP056.001.050.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 April 12; UP056.001.050.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 April 18; UP056.001.050.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 April 26; UP056.001.050.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 May 03; UP056.001.050.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 May 10; UP056.001.050.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 May 17; UP056.001.050.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 21 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 September 13; UP056.001.051.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 September 27; UP056.001.051.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Isabel Abbott, Appointed Director of Admissions (substituting for Mrs. Lovejoy on sick leave), p. 6.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 October 04; UP056.001.051.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 October 11; UP056.001.051.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 October 18; UP056.001.051.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 October 25; UP056.001.051.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Academic Honors; p.6. [Alpha Sigma Phi] Eight brothers donate blood at Tufts Surgical Center of Boston City Hospital [Includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 November 01; UP056.001.051.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 November 08; UP056.001.051.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 51)
    American institute of electrical engineering; Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of.; Academic Honors; pp. 1,5. [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly ALpha Xi Delta).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 November 15; UP056.001.051.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 November 22; UP056.001.051.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 December 06; UP056.001.051.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 December 13; UP056.001.051.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi; [Robert Alukonis, A1958] Paul Perito, preparing for a career in profesional or educational field
  - Tufts Weekly, 1957 December 20; UP056.001.051.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 January 10; UP056.001.051.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 January 23; UP056.001.051.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 February 03; UP056.001.051.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 February 07; UP056.001.051.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 February 14; UP056.001.051.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
    All Around Club; Alpha Xi Delta to be reactivated
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 February 19; UP056.001.051.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 February 21; UP056.001.051.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 February 28; UP056.001.051.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Administration] Plus-minus marks. p. 5. All Around Club; Alpha Xi Delta to be reactivated
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 05; UP056.001.051.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] Student council opposed to reinstatement
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 07; UP056.001.051.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 12; UP056.001.051.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Administration] Plus-minus marks. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 14; UP056.001.051.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 19; UP056.001.051.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 21; UP056.001.051.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 March 26; UP056.001.051.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 01; UP056.001.051.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 09; UP056.001.051.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 11; UP056.001.051.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 16; UP056.001.051.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 18; UP056.001.051.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 23; UP056.001.051.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 25; UP056.001.051.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 29; UP056.001.051.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 April 30; UP056.001.051.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 May 02; UP056.001.051.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Alpha Tau Omega. [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta). All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 May 07; UP056.001.051.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 May 09; UP056.001.051.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 May 14; UP056.001.051.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 May 16; UP056.001.051.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 May 21; UP056.001.051.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta). Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 June 07; UP056.001.051.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 June 08; UP056.001.051.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Academic Ceremonies 1958-59. Photo of academic procession.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 June 09; UP056.001.051.00046 (Volume Shared 134)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 September 12; UP056.001.052.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 September 17; UP056.001.052.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [Alumni council] Twenty-fifth anniversary
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 September 19; UP056.001.052.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 September 24; UP056.001.052.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 September 26; UP056.001.052.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [Administration] Plus-minus marks. To be put into effect Fall, 1958. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 01; UP056.001.052.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 03; UP056.001.052.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Daniel C. Abbott (faculty). Director of orchestra and teacher of chorus. (page 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 08; UP056.001.052.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 10; UP056.001.052.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 15; UP056.001.052.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 17; UP056.001.052.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 22; UP056.001.052.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [American association of teachers of french] Tufts host Boston chapter
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 24; UP056.001.052.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 29; UP056.001.052.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 October 31; UP056.001.052.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 05; UP056.001.052.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 07; UP056.001.052.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 12; UP056.001.052.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 14; UP056.001.052.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 19; UP056.001.052.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 21; UP056.001.052.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 November 25; UP056.001.052.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 December 03; UP056.001.052.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 December 05; UP056.001.052.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 December 10; UP056.001.052.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 December 12; UP056.001.052.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958 December 18; UP056.001.052.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 January 09; UP056.001.052.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 January 14; UP056.001.052.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 January 16; UP056.001.052.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 04; UP056.001.052.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 06; UP056.001.052.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 11; UP056.001.052.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Poet Wilbur Reads at Cohen Monday
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 13; UP056.001.052.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 18; UP056.001.052.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Dr. Crook named Psychology Head
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 20; UP056.001.052.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Convalescing from illness, p. 1. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 February 27; UP056.001.052.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Convalescing from illness, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 04; UP056.001.052.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Convalescing from illness, p. 5.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 06; UP056.001.052.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    U Thittila, Buddhist Monk, VIists Tufts Community for Five Days; Class Appearances Highlight Stay
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 11; UP056.001.052.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Debating Society places second in Hofstra meet
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 13; UP056.001.052.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [President Herbert] Hoover Recieves Ballou Medal
    Hoover, Herbert C.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 18; UP056.001.052.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Interdorm Award at Jackson
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 20; UP056.001.052.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Council Hears Negative Mayorality Sentiment; [American association of teacher of french] French speaking contest
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 March 26; UP056.001.052.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta). Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 April 08; UP056.001.052.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Oxford Chemist Gives Science and Religion Lecture on Friday
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 April 10; UP056.001.052.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Christie Allan (J 1962) Performs in "Ice Chips" presented by Skating Club of Boston.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 April 15; UP056.001.052.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Alpha Sigma Phi. Freeland K. Abbott, (faculty) 1959, Recipient of U.S. Educational grant under auspices of Fulbright Act to conduct research in contemporary Islam at University of Karachi in Pakistan, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 April 17; UP056.001.052.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 April 24; UP056.001.052.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 April 29; UP056.001.052.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Space Exposition Opens here Friday
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 May 01; UP056.001.052.00051 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 May 06; UP056.001.052.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 May 13; UP056.001.052.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Dr. Rethis Lectures at Tufts tomorrow night; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 May 15; UP056.001.052.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Prof. Frederick Weaver Retires after 40 years
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 May 21; UP056.001.052.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Fletcher School Celebrates 25th Anniversary. Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 June 06; UP056.001.052.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Alumni day; [Allen, George V.] Speaker at Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Commencement banquet, 1959.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 September 19; UP056.001.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 September 25; UP056.001.053.00002 (Box 53)
    [Administration] Changes in [administration]. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 October 02; UP056.001.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 October 09; UP056.001.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 October 16; UP056.001.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 October 23; UP056.001.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 October 30; UP056.001.053.00007 (Box 53)
    Freeland K. Abbott, In Pakistan doing research on "Social and Cultural Changes in Islam and Pakistan," p. 9.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 November 06; UP056.001.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 November 13; UP056.001.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 November 20; UP056.001.053.00010 (Box 53)
    [Admissions] Administered under John C. Palmer. p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 December 04; UP056.001.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 December 11; UP056.001.053.00012 (Box 53)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi; [alumni council] Committee formed to standardize college colors; [American association of University Professors] Tufts chapter chides mandatory oaths for federal loans
  - Tufts Weekly, 1959 December 17; UP056.001.053.00013 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 January 08; UP056.001.053.00014 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 January 15; UP056.001.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 January 21; UP056.001.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 February 12; UP056.001.053.00017 (Box 53)
    [Allen, Catherine L.] Coordinator of Special Activities.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 February 19; UP056.001.053.00018 (Box 53)
    [alumni council] Committee formed to standardize college colors; [Administration] Faculty group appointed by Administrative Registration Study Committee studies registration. p. 5. [Administration] Faculty group appointed by Administrative Registration Study Committee studies registration.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 February 26; UP056.001.053.00019 (Box 53)
    [Alumni council] New policy offers courses to alumni, faculty, staff members and friends
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 March 04; UP056.001.053.00020 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 March 11; UP056.001.053.00021 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 March 18; UP056.001.053.00022 (Box 53)
    Academy of American Poets; Poetry contest open to Tufts students; P.6.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 March 25; UP056.001.053.00023 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 March 31; UP056.001.053.00024 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 April 01; UP056.001.053.00025 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 April 15; UP056.001.053.00026 (Box 53)
    Alethea Sorority. [All Around Club] Father-Daughter Weekend. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 April 22; UP056.001.053.00027 (Box 53)
    [All Around Club] Father-Daughter Weekend.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 April 29; UP056.001.053.00028 (Box 53)
    [All Around Club] Father-Daughter Weekend. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 May 05; UP056.001.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 May 06; UP056.001.053.00030 (Box 53)
    Alpha Sigma Phi; [American association of teacher of spanish and portuguese] Tufts host to Boston Spanish contest of the Pan American society of New England
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 May 13; UP056.001.053.00031 (Box 53)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] Action to reactivate
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 May 20; UP056.001.053.00032 (Box 53)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi; [Alpha Xi Delta] action to reactivate not approved; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 September 16; UP056.001.054.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 September 23; UP056.001.054.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 September 30; UP056.001.054.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 October 07; UP056.001.054.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 54)
    [All Around Club] Activities. [Alpha Omicron Pi] Tufts Chapter to be hostesses to regional convention on Jackson campus.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 October 14; UP056.001.054.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 54)
    [alumni council] Panel Discussions: "The Gentlemen's C - passing or passe"
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 October 21; UP056.001.054.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 54)
    [alumni council] Panel Discussions: "The Gentlemen's C - passing or passe"; Freeland K. Abbott (faculty). Returns from research expedition in Pakistan, p. 7.; Academic Honors; P.1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 October 28; UP056.001.054.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 November 04; UP056.001.054.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 54)
    Academic Honors; Icludes photos of William Meserve, Jerome Loeb, Shali Zysman, Dorothy Murphy, Terry McGarry, etc...pp. 1,8.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 November 10; UP056.001.054.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 November 12; UP056.001.054.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 November 18; UP056.001.054.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 December 02; UP056.001.054.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1960 December 09; UP056.001.054.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 54)